import { type accordion } from "~/components/Accordion";

export const sixDayAmboseliMaasaiMaraSafari: accordion[] = [
    {
      question: "Day 1: Amboseli National Park",
      answer: "Welcome to your safari adventure! After meeting our team, we’ll explain the next steps and set out to Amboseli National Park, where Mt. Kilimanjaro provides a stunning backdrop. Famous for its large elephant population and diverse wildlife, Amboseli offers a classic safari experience.",
      listHeader: "Activities Day 1",
      list: [
        "Morning: Transfer by Road, Jomo Kenyatta International Airport to Wilson Airstrip",
        "Mid-morning: Transfer by Air, Wilson Airstrip to Amboseli National Park",
        "Afternoon: Afternoon game drive, Amboseli National Park",
        "Late Afternoon: Leisure"
      ]
    },
    {
      question: "Day 2: Amboseli National Park",
      answer: "Explore Amboseli further with game drives that provide excellent opportunities to see elephants, lions, cheetahs, and more, along with beautiful birdwatching. Optionally, visit a Maasai village for a cultural experience.",
      listHeader: "Activities Day 2",
      list: [
        "Morning & Afternoon: Game drive, Amboseli National Park",
        "Late Afternoon: Leisure",
        "Optional Afternoon: Masai cultural visit, Amboseli National Park"
      ]
    },
    {
      question: "Day 3-5: Masai Mara National Reserve",
      answer: "Embark on a thrilling safari in the Masai Mara National Reserve, renowned for its abundant big cats and stunning landscapes. Enjoy daily game drives, and optionally, take a breathtaking balloon safari over the Mara plains.",
      listHeader: "Activities Day 3",
      list: [
        "Mid-morning: Transfer by Air, Amboseli National Park to Masai Mara National Reserve",
        "Afternoon: Afternoon game drive, Masai Mara National Reserve",
        "Late Afternoon: Leisure"
      ],
      listHeader2: "Activities Day 4",
      list2: [
        "Morning & Afternoon: Game drive, Masai Mara National Reserve",
        "Afternoon: Leisure"
      ],
      listHeader3: "Activities Day 5",
      list3: [
        "Morning & Afternoon: Game drive, Masai Mara National Reserve",
        "Late Afternoon: Leisure",
        "Optional Afternoon: Masai cultural visit, Masai Mara National Reserve",
        "Optional Early Morning: Balloon safari over the Masai Mara"
      ]
    },
    {
      question: "Day 6: Nairobi City",
      answer: "Conclude your safari with a final game drive in the Masai Mara. Afterward, transfer back to Nairobi for your return journey. We hope you leave with unforgettable memories of your time in Kenya.",
      listHeader: "Activities Day 6",
      list: [
        "Early Morning: Game drive, Masai Mara National Reserve",
        "Mid-morning: Transfer by Air, Masai Mara National Reserve to Wilson Airstrip",
        "Afternoon: Transfer by Road, Wilson Airstrip to Jomo Kenyatta International Airport",
        "On arrival: End of services, Nairobi city"
      ]
    }
  ];
  
export const fourDaysAndBeyondInKenya: accordion[] = [
    {
      question: "Day 1: Mara Triangle Conservancy",
      answer: "The Mara Triangle, located within the Masai Mara National Reserve, offers an exclusive safari experience with its breathtaking landscapes and rich wildlife. Known for the Great Migration, this area allows you to witness thrilling encounters with lions, elephants, cheetahs, and even elusive leopards in a less crowded setting.",
      listHeader: "Activities Day 1",
      list: [
        "Morning: Transfer by Air, Wilson Airstrip to Kichwa Tembo airstrip",
        "Mid-morning: Transfer by Air, Kichwa Tembo airstrip to Masai Mara National Reserve",
        "Afternoon: Afternoon game drive, Masai Mara National Reserve",
        "Dinner: Dinner"
      ],
      listHeader2: "Meal Plan",
      list2: ["Lunch & Dinner"]
    },
    {
      question: "Day 2: Mara Triangle Conservancy",
      answer: "Continue exploring the stunning Mara Triangle, where the vibrant ecosystem offers unmatched opportunities to spot wildlife amidst the iconic Mara River and open savannahs.",
      listHeader: "Activities Day 2",
      list: [
        "Morning: Morning game drive, Masai Mara National Reserve",
        "Afternoon: Lunch break",
        "Late Afternoon: Afternoon game drive, Masai Mara National Reserve"
      ],
      listHeader2: "Meal Plan",
      list2: ["Breakfast, Lunch & Dinner"]
    },
    {
      question: "Day 3: Mara Triangle Conservancy",
      answer: "Spend another memorable day in the Masai Mara, enjoying both game drives and a special picnic lunch amidst the beautiful wilderness.",
      listHeader: "Activities Day 3",
      list: [
        "Morning: Morning game drive, Masai Mara National Reserve",
        "Lunch: Picnic in Masai Mara National Reserve",
        "Afternoon: Afternoon game drive, Masai Mara National Reserve",
        "Dinner: Dinner"
      ],
      listHeader2: "Meal Plan",
      list2: ["Breakfast, Lunch & Dinner"]
    },
    {
      question: "Day 4: Nairobi City",
      answer: "As your safari draws to a close, enjoy a final morning game drive before returning to Nairobi. We hope you carry home cherished memories of this unforgettable experience.",
      listHeader: "Activities Day 4",
      list: [
        "Morning: Morning game drive, Masai Mara National Reserve",
        "Mid-morning: Transfer by Road to Kichwa Tembo airstrip",
        "On arrival: Transfer by Air, Kichwa Tembo airstrip to Wilson Airport",
        "End of services, Nairobi city"
      ],
      listHeader2: "Meal Plan",
      list2: ["Breakfast"]
    }
  ];
  
  export const fiveDaysTemboSafariAmboseliandTsavo: accordion[] = [
    {
      question: "Day 1 & 2: Amboseli National Park",
      answer: "Begin your safari journey with us as we introduce you to Amboseli National Park. Known for its stunning views of Mt Kilimanjaro and close encounters with elephants, Amboseli offers some of the best wildlife experiences in Kenya. Capture unforgettable moments with elephants, lions, cheetahs, and more, all set against the breathtaking backdrop of Africa's highest peak.",
      listHeader: "Activities Day 1 & 2",
      list: [
        "Day 1 Morning: Airport meet and greet, Jomo Kenyatta International Airport",
        "Day 1 Morning: Transfer by Road, Jomo Kenyatta International Airport to Amboseli National Park",
        "Day 2 Morning & Afternoon: Guided game drive through Amboseli National Park",
        "Day 2 Evening: Leisure, Amboseli National Park"
      ],
      listHeader2: "Meal Plan",
      list2: ["Lunch & Dinner (Day 1), Breakfast, Lunch & Dinner (Day 2)"]
    },
    {
      question: "Day 3 & 4: Tsavo East National Park",
      answer: "Explore the vast and rugged landscapes of Tsavo East, one of Kenya's largest parks, famous for its 'red' elephants and unique wildlife. You'll encounter lions, cheetahs, Somali ostriches, and perhaps even the rare hirola antelope. Nearly 500 bird species have also been recorded here, making it a birdwatcher’s paradise.",
      listHeader: "Activities Day 3 & 4",
      list: [
        "Day 3 Morning: Transfer by Air, Amboseli National Park to Tsavo East National Park",
        "Day 3 Mid-morning: Transfer by Road, Airstrip to Tsavo East National Park",
        "Day 3 Afternoon: Guided game drive through Tsavo East National Park",
        "Day 4 Morning & Afternoon: Guided game drive through Tsavo East National Park",
        "Day 4 Evening: Leisure, Tsavo East National Park"
      ],
      listHeader2: "Meal Plan",
      list2: ["Breakfast, Lunch & Dinner (both days)"]
    },
    {
      question: "Day 5: Nairobi City",
      answer: "As your safari draws to a close, enjoy a final morning in Tsavo East before returning to Nairobi. We hope you leave with cherished memories of this remarkable adventure and look forward to welcoming you back on safari in the future.",
      listHeader: "Activities Day 5",
      list: [
        "Mid-morning: Transfer by Road, Tsavo East National Park to Airstrip",
        "Mid-Day: Transfer by Air, Tsavo East National Park to Wilson Airstrip",
        "Afternoon: Transfer by Road, Wilson Airstrip to Jomo Kenyatta International Airport"
      ],
      listHeader2: "Meal Plan",
      list2: ["Breakfast"]
    }
  ];